[{"answer": "I think when investigators get through with this letter, they're going to have a good idea of who this guy is, if he indeed wrote this letter in 2004.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "I want you to bring me up to speed with what is in this letter and how significant it may turn out to be in understanding the kind of person Ariel Castro is?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "It just is extraordinary, isn't it?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "At first I never thought anything of it until I started hearing all the news, stuff about him, and thinking about it now, I'm like it could be, maybe he resented these women who they didn't want to dance with him for whatever the reasons were.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "And do you feel, Tito, that that kind of persistent rejection with women may have played a part in all this behavioral deficiency that developed inside him?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "When I went to his house two years ago, like I say, I sold him some appliances.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "When you think about it now with hindsight, it makes more sense?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "No, everybody's been shocked, shocked to the point where they really don't want to talk about it.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Can anyone quite believe that Ariel Castro, this apparently nice, normal guy, has turned out to be allegedly this horrific monster?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Very good, Piers.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "That's definitely true, Piers.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Is there a sense of, yes, great joy these women have been found, but also a sense of collective guilt that the community and the police and everyone working together were unable to find any of them in ten years?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "You believe that he was a bit of a manipulator, is that right?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well, with stuff like that.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Why did you fire him?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I actually heard -- March 13, I got some texts from him, of this year, that he really wanted to come back with the band.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "When did you last hear from him?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Honestly, Mr. Morgan, I didn't.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Looking back on the time you spent with him, particularly at the house, was there anything that happened in all that time that when you look at it now, you think, OK, now I get what may have been going on?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "No, I only saw the very social, happy go lucky guy on the block.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Did you see any of that?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "He was -- we don't know.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Other than shock, what are you all thinking?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Do you feel guilty, Juan, that you were so close to these girls and you weren't able to help them, even though you knew nothing about what was happening?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Do you think now he was using -- not yours, but some of the others, right?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "He had dogs in that yard.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "But do you think his intention, Storm, in doing this was to hide out any possible noises from his -- the women that he captured?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "He's up there.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Where does this man, Ariel Castro, assuming he gets convicted of all the crimes we believe he's done -- where does he rank in your eyes?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "When you get an offender at this age, in his 40s like this, usually, it begins -- OK, let's give you a this is your life kind of thing with violent offenders.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "John, the big question, I guess, is could there be other serious crimes that Ariel Castro has committed, given that this period only starts, really, in his 40s?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Very definitely.", "docId": "130510pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Do you think, John, that if Amanda Berry hasn't shown the courage she did to escape at the start of this week, that her own daughter that she had with this man could have come into his target- range, in terms of being a sexual tool for him?", "qSentId": 519}]